Let's apply what we just learned by opening up
让我们应用一下我们刚刚学的打开
the MainActivity.java file within our project. We're going to take
我们工程中的MainActivity.java文件，我们将要用
this networking code snippet and move it over to
这些网络代码片段并且移动它到
it's own AsyncTask, so it runs in a background
我们自己的异步任务中，如此他就运行在一个
thread. The task is going to be defined within
背景线程上。这个任务将被定义在
this fragment class. But speaking of which, it's actually
这个片段类里。但是说到这里，他确实
still called PlaceholderFragment. Let's do a little bit of
还叫PlaceholderFragment.让我们做一点小小的
refactoring now by giving it a real name. Let's call
重整通过给她一个真是的名字。那我们就叫她
it ForecastFragment. And then you can update it
ForecastFragment.然后你也可以更新她
in other appropriate places as well. We can also
在其他的适当的地方。我们也可以
move ForecastFragment into its own file that way
移动ForecastFragment到我们自己的文件里
the MainActivity won't get so long and cumbersome. Within
这样MainActivity就不会显得那么长那么嗦。在
ForecastFragment we should define a new inner class
ForecastFragment里我们应该定义一个新的内部类
called FetchWeatherTask which extends from AsyncTask. And then you
叫做FetchWeatherTask,她扩展自AsyncTask。然后你
can move the networking code snippet here. After you
可以移动网络代码片段。在你
make the changes and run your app, it should
做完调整并且运行你的应用程序之后，他应该
look something like this. There really should be no difference except it
看起来像这个。那就应该没有区别
doesn't crash now. In the next step we will add code to execute
除了她现在不能崩溃，在接下来的这一步中我们将要添加代码去执行
the task. And later in the lesson, we'll do JSON parsing and updating
这个任务。在这节课的最后，我们将要做JSON语法分析并且更新
the UI. In the meantime though, make these initial changes to your code.
UI。在这期间，让这些基础修改你的代码吧